http://www.thrombogenics.com/privacy-policy

Symptomatic VMA/VMT
PipelineTHR-149 (PKal Inhibitor)
THR-687 (pan RGD integrin antagonist)
Symptomatic VMA/VMT
PipelineTHR-149 (PKal Inhibitor)
THR-687 (pan RGD integrin antagonist)
Privacy policy
Developing next generation treatments to preserve vision for patients with diseases affecting the back of the eye
Privacy PolicyThis Privacy Statement sets out how Oxurion NV and ThromboGenics Inc. (subsidiary of Oxurion NV) uses and protects any information that you give to us. We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting your personal information. This Privacy Statement explains how we collect, transfer, process, store, use and disclose your data and sets out our security practices.
By providing us with your personal information, you agree and consent to its transfer, processing, storage, use and disclosure as outlined in this Privacy Statement. You may revoke your consent at any time.
What we collect
Personal data is data that identifies you as an individual. We collect personal data that you provide to us. We only do this when you have agreed to our request for that information. This personal data may include:
name
address
telephone number
e-mail address
If you encounter an adverse event or product complaint and submit it through the relevant form on the website, we ask you for additional information, some of which may be sensitive information. By not providing some of this information, you may be putting yourself, or someone else at risk. We will also contact you concerning the information you provide to us. This data will be collected and retained in accordance with the regulations for reporting these events. This data will also be protected using the measures that we have in place (see “How we protect your personal data”). By providing the information, you are consenting to its use.
How we use your personal data
By providing your personal data, you agree that, where it is permitted by local law or where you have agreed to receiving these communications from us, we may use the information to:
respond to your requests
improve our level of service
improve the content of our communications
notify you of our new products and services
seek your views on our products and services
consider your application for employment (via Jobs page)
If you later change your mind and no longer wish to receive any further information from us, you may unsubscribe from these communications at any time and you will be removed from our mailing lists.
Website usage information
We also automatically collect information about your computer browser type and operating system, Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. We aggregate this information to understand how our visitors use our website so that we can improve them and the services we offer.
How we protect your personal data
We will take appropriate legal, organisational, and technical measures to protect your personal information consistent with applicable privacy and data security laws. When Oxurion uses a third-party service provider, that provider will be carefully selected and required to use appropriate measures to protect the privacy and security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal data from unauthorised access, use or disclosure. We cannot guarantee the security of the transmission of information via the Internet connection as it is not completely secure. Any transmission is at your own risk. While we cannot guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration to data will not occur, once we have received your information, we will employ appropriate technical security measures to prevent loss, misuse, alteration or similar such unfortunate events.
Sharing of personal data with third parties
We may share your personal data with our affiliates, contractors and agents in the normal course of business for delivery of the activities to which you have agreed. Unless otherwise specified in the website, we will not sell or rent personal data to other third parties, except that your data may be transferred to a third party in the event that the business of this site or a part of it and the customer data connected with it is sold, assigned or transferred. Sometimes we use selected third parties to provide support services in connection with our websites or in the normal course of business. These parties may, from time to time, have access to your information to enable them to provide those services to us. We require all companies providing such support services to meet the same standards of data protection as our own. They are prohibited from using the information for their own purposes. In particular, we do not allow service providers to use your personal data for their own marketing activities.
When we may disclose your personal data to others
Oxurion reserves the right to disclose personal information about you, including your e-mail address, for reporting to government authorities, to parties in relevant legal proceedings as authorised by the presiding court or tribunal and otherwise to the extent required or explicitly authorised by applicable law. In certain special cases where permitted by local law, we may disclose your personal data:
when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to you or otherwise injuring or interfering with Oxurion rights, property or operations, other users of this website or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities
when we believe the law requires it, or in response to any demand by law enforcement authorities in connection with a criminal investigation, or civil or administrative authorities in connection with a pending civil case or administrative investigation
in the event of a merger, acquisition, consolidation, asset sale or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy.
In each of the cases above, the Data Protection Officer will determine the legitimacy of the request prior to the disclosure.
Storage of Personal Data
Personal data collected may be transferred to, stored and processed in your country of residence or a country in which Oxurion, subcontractors or agents maintain facilities, including the United States and countries outside the European Economic Area (EEA). This means that your information may be processed in countries with lower data protection standards than your country of residence. By using our website, you consent to any transfer, processing or storing of information outside of your country of residence and outside the EEA. We will ensure that if information is transferred outside your country of residence, it will still be treated in accordance with this Privacy Statement.
Use of IP addresses
An IP address is a set of numbers that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you log on to your Internet service provider or through your organisation's local area network (LAN) or wide area network (WAN). Web servers automatically identify your computer by the IP address assigned to it during your session online.
Oxurion, or third party companies acting on our behalf, may collect IP addresses for the purposes of systems administration and to audit the use of our websites. We also may use IP addresses to identify users of our websites when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with the websites’ terms of use or to protect our service, websites or other users.
Cookies
A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a server. Cookies allow our website to respond to you as an individual. The website can tailor its operations to your needs, by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies or receive a warning before a cookie is stored if you prefer. Please refer to your Internet browser help page to learn more about these functions and to specify your cookie preferences.
If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of our website or any other websites that you visit.
Information from outside sources
Where permitted by local law, we may also collect legally obtained information from third parties to add to our existing user databases. Some of this information may be personal data. We do this to better target information offerings and promotional campaigns in which we think you would be interested. Such personal data will only be collected and used by us in accordance with the basis on which it was originally provided by the subject, or as otherwise permitted by local law.
Access
We will retain your information only for the period necessary to fulfil the purposes outlined in this Privacy Statement unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law. Only those employees or third party contractors with legitimate business needs will have access to the data that you provide.
Your Rights
You may contact us in writing to request the updating, correction or removal of any personal data that you have provided to us at any time using the contact information provided at the end of this Privacy Statement. Within the EEA, you may make these requests, free of charge. We will also return your data to you, if required.
We will comply with your request within a reasonable time frame unless there is a legitimate reason for us to maintain your data (for example, a regulatory or legal requirement). If this is the case, we will inform you and provide the reason why we are unable to comply with your request.
You may unsubscribe from any mailing lists at any time by using the link provided in the emails you receive.
Links to other websites
Our website may from time to time provide links to third party websites. This Privacy Statement does not apply to those websites. If you choose to enter such a linked site, you agree that we are not responsible for the availability of such websites and do not review or endorse and shall not be liable, directly or indirectly, for the content or the use of your personal data or the use that others make of these external websites.
Please ensure you check the legal and privacy statements posted on each website you access before entering any personal data.
Use of our website by children
Unless otherwise explicitly stated, the website on which this Privacy Statement appears is not intended or designed to attract children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal data from visitors in that age group via these websites.
Changes
Oxurion may periodically change, modify, add, remove or otherwise update this Policy at its discretion, without prior notification. However, any changes to this Statement will be posted on this page so that you are fully informed of the types of information we are gathering, how we use it, and under what circumstances it may be disclosed.
If you have any concerns related to this Privacy Statement or general concerns about the privacy and security of your personal data, the Data Protection Officer at Oxurion can be contacted via:
Oxurion NV
1 Gaston Geenslaan
3001 Leuven
Belgium
+32 16 75 13 10
privacy@oxurion.com
About usOxurion at a glance
Our milestones
